https://www.restoringorder.com/privacy-policy/

Updated: May 25, 2018
This Privacy Policy applies to the Restoring Order, LLC, website (“RO” and “Site”). This Privacy Policy describes the information RO collects on the Site, how it is used, and your options with respect to its use. By accessing or using this Site you indicate your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to be bound by this Privacy Policy do not access or use this Site. Please also review RO’s terms of use of which this Privacy Policy is a part.
Your privacy is important Restoring Order and this policy represents our commitment to safeguard and protect your personal information. This policy governs use of the RestoringOrder.com website (the “Site”), which is provided by Restoring Order as Restoring Order, an Oregon Limited Liability Company, LLC (“we,” “us” or “our”). This Privacy Policy governs our collection of information from you (“you,” “your” or a “user”) through your use of the Site. It does not apply to any information you may provide to us through other means, including via mail or telephone. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our online privacy practices.
RESTORING ORDER RESPECTS YOUR PRIVACY.
We use Google Analytics to track GENERAL usership data so that we can ensure Restoring Order is found by those looking for organizing and life reclamation services. If you do not want to work with companies who use Google Analytics, you should discontinue your use of RestoringOrder.com. We use Google Analytics because:
We are interested in where users are landing on our site and what they’re doing once they arrive so that we can ensure our site is navigable and useful to users
We do make course corrections to improve our sites based on that data
We do NOT however, seek or keep information associated with specific IP addresses (ie: individual users)
Restoring Order ONLY gathers contact information from those who have requested our resources or contact with us.
BY VISITING THE SITE YOU AGREE THAT YOUR VISIT, AND ANY DISPUTE OVER OUR ONLINE PRIVACY PRACTICES, IS GOVERNED BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT. We use the information gathered to better understand your needs, to improve the contents of our web pages and to monitor technical performance of our network.
The information we gather falls into three categories: (1) information voluntarily supplied by users to the Site through optional registration; and (2) tracking information gathered as users navigate through the Site; and (3) order, form, shipping, and payment information gathered through our store.
Information You Provide To Us.
We may collect and store information, personal or otherwise, that you voluntarily supply either while using our Site or in responding via email in connection with a feature provided on our Site. Some examples of this type of information include demographic information and personal information (such as your name, address, or email address, along with profile information such as a password or passphrase) that you electronically submit to Us for purposes such as registration for certain features on our Site, signing up for email newsletters, completing surveys or entering sweepstakes, or posting on message boards or other public posting areas on our Site. We may also ask for information (including a credit card number) from users who make a purchase or conduct other transactions on our Site. The information supplied helps us to provide the product or service requested, offer you more personalized features, and tailor the Site to your interests. Supplying such information is entirely voluntary. However, if you choose not to supply information requested, we may be unable to provide you with services offered to users of the Site.
Tracking Information.
We also may collect and store information that is generated automatically as you navigate through our Site. For example, to help make the Site more responsive to the needs of users, we employ a standard feature of browser software called a “cookie” to assign each user a unique, random number that resides on a user’s computer. The cookie does not personally identify the user; it merely identifies the computer with which the user accesses the Site. Unless a user voluntarily identifies himself or herself (through registration, for example), the Site will not be able to ascertain the identity of the user, even if a cookie is assigned to a user’s computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information supplied by a user. By showing how and when visitors use the Site, cookies help us track user trends and patterns. They also prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of the Site where you have entered preference information previously. Of course, you are free to set your web browser to disable cookies; however, doing so may render your computer unable to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other users of the Site.
We also may use web beacons and other methods to access cookies and to count users who visit our Site or open our HTML-formatted email messages. Our Site’s servers automatically collect limited information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, including your IP address. The IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send data such as the web pages users view. An IP address does not personally identify a user. We use this information to deliver the Site’s content to you upon request and to measure traffic within the Site.
We may use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information about users of our Site and about activity that occurs within our Site, and we may use this information to, among other things, serve targeted information including offers on our Site. The information collected allows us to analyze how users use the Site and to track user interests, trends and patterns. We also may use third-party advertising, and the companies providing this advertising may use their own cookies, web beacons and similar technologies. These companies may use that information, sometimes in conjunction with similar non-personally identifiable information gathered from other websites, to deliver advertisements on this Site, and possibly on other websites (if the third-party advertising company operates an advertising network), tailored to match the perceived interests of consumers. The collection and use of information by these companies is governed by the relevant third party’s privacy policy and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We do not have access to cookies that may be placed on your computer by third-party ad technology, ad servers or ad networks.
USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION. We use the information we collect in a variety of ways, including using the information to customize features and advertising that appear on the Site. We also may provide your information to third parties, such as service providers, contractors, and sponsors, for a variety of purposes.
You agree that we may use your information to contact you for customer service purposes, to inform you of important changes or additions to our Site or the services offered over our Site, and to send you administrative notices, offers and any other communications that we believe may be of interest to you. You may withdraw your permission and prevent our use of your information in this manner by contacting us using the contact information below.
We reserve the right to disclose to third parties all of the information that we collect online about you and other visitors, with one important exception – we will not share your credit card number or other financial information with any third party unrelated to an authorized transaction, unless such disclosure is required by law. We may, however, share non-financial information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Please bear in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties online – for example on ratings and reviews or through email – that information can be seen, collected and used by others besides us. We cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third-party use of such information.
Please be aware that we may occasionally release information about users when release is appropriate to comply with law or to enforce or protect the rights, property or safety of other users of our Site, the public or us.
MODIFYING YOUR INFORMATION AND OPTING OUT. If you register with us, you will have the opportunity to review, receive, update, change or delete the information you have provided to us (and that we continue to store) at any time. Please contact us by phone, email, or postal mail using the information below.
STORAGE OF INFORMATION. All information gathered on our Site is stored within a database accessible only by us. We will use industry standard measures, including encryption where appropriate. However, as effective as the reasonable security measures we implement may be, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information supplied will not be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet. To the extent permitted by law, in no event shall we be liable for the deletion, loss, or unauthorized modification of any of your information.
ADDITIONAL INFORMATION ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY. Restoring Order does not publish text, images, or multimedia content that portrays nudity, foul language, violence, or other information not suitable for children. The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13 and we will not knowingly maintain personally identifiable information from or about anyone under 13.
CHANGES TO THIS POLICY. The Internet and relevant state and federal law is always evolving. If we need to change this Privacy Policy at some point in the future, we’ll post the modified Privacy Policy on this Site and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. If you are concerned with how your information is used you should check this webpage periodically. By continuing to use the Site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified.
ADDITIONAL PRIVACY QUESTIONS? If you have any questions or concerns about Restoring Order’s Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@restoringorder.com, by phone to 503-625-5774.
Pin It on Pinterest
[gravityform id="44" title="false" description="false"]
<div class='gf_browser_unknown gform_wrapper' id='gform_wrapper_44' ><form method='post' enctype='multipart/form-data'
id='gform_44'
action='/privacy-policy/'>
<div class='gform_body'><ul id='gform_fields_44' class='gform_fields top_label form_sublabel_below description_below'><li id='field_44_1'
class='gfield gfield_contains_required field_sublabel_below field_description_below gfield_visibility_visible' ><label class='gfield_label gfield_label_before_complex'
>Name<span class='gfield_required'>*</span></label><div class='ginput_complex ginput_container no_prefix has_first_name no_middle_name has_last_name no_suffix gf_name_has_2 ginput_container_name' id='input_44_1'>
<span id='input_44_1_3_container' class='name_first' >
<input type='text' name='input_1.3' id='input_44_1_3' value='' aria-label='First name'
aria-required="true" aria-invalid="false" />
<label for='input_44_1_3' >First</label>
</span>
<span id='input_44_1_6_container' class='name_last' >
<input type='text' name='input_1.6' id='input_44_1_6' value='' aria-label='Last name'
aria-required="true" aria-invalid="false" />
<label for='input_44_1_6' >Last</label>
</span>
</div></li><li id='field_44_2'
class='gfield gfield_contains_required field_sublabel_below field_description_below gfield_visibility_visible' ><label class='gfield_label' for='input_44_2' >Email<span class='gfield_required'>*</span></label><div class='ginput_container ginput_container_email'>
<input name='input_2' id='input_44_2' type='text' value='' class='large'
aria-required="true" aria-invalid="false" />
</div></li><li id='field_44_3'
class='gfield gform_validation_container field_sublabel_below field_description_below gfield_visibility_visible' ><label class='gfield_label' for='input_44_3' >Comments</label><div class='ginput_container'><input name='input_3' id='input_44_3' type='text' value='' /></div><div class='gfield_description' id='gfield_description_44_3'>This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.</div></li>
</ul></div>
<div class='gform_footer top_label'> <input type='submit' id='gform_submit_button_44' class='gform_button button' value='Send Now »'
onclick='if(window["gf_submitting_44"]){return false;}
window["gf_submitting_44"]=true;
' onkeypress='if( event.keyCode == 13 ){ if(window["gf_submitting_44"]){return false;} window["gf_submitting_44"]=true;
jQuery("#gform_44").trigger("submit",[true]); }' />
<input type='hidden' class='gform_hidden' name='is_submit_44' value='1' />
<input type='hidden' class='gform_hidden' name='gform_submit' value='44' />
<input type='hidden' class='gform_hidden' name='gform_unique_id' value='' />
<input type='hidden' class='gform_hidden' name='state_44' value='WyJbXSIsIjZlMzVlMWQ3OTM2OGRlNzE0YjU5MjQyZGM4YjViNTQzIl0=' />
<input type='hidden' class='gform_hidden' name='gform_target_page_number_44' id='gform_target_page_number_44' value='0' />
<input type='hidden' class='gform_hidden' name='gform_source_page_number_44' id='gform_source_page_number_44' value='1' />
<input type='hidden' name='gform_field_values' value='' />
</div>
</form>
</div><script type='text/javascript'> jQuery(document).bind('gform_post_render', function(event, formId, currentPage){if(formId == 44) {} } );jQuery(document).bind('gform_post_conditional_logic', function(event, formId, fields, isInit){} );</script><script type='text/javascript'> jQuery(document).ready(function(){jQuery(document).trigger('gform_post_render', [44, 1]) } ); </script>
